Hello friends, if you have recently
insured your bike from policybazar.com
and its KYC is pending and
you have not even downloaded the insurance policy,
then friends, in this video
we will learn how to complete the KYC
and how to download the insurance policy.
So friends, you
will know all this information in this video.  So friends, let's go to the
computer and mobile screen.  So
friends, you must have
given a Gmail ID while doing bike insurance on policybazar.com.
You have to open that Gmail ID.
In that you might have received an email from policy ba.
You have to click on this mail SMS
and you will see this type of interface of mail SMS.
Complete
KYC: So friends, you have to
click on the Complete KYC option,
you have to wait a little and a new page will
open.
In this you will see an option
Upload Documents and Complete
KYC.  You have to click on this option.   I have to
wait a little.
So friends, you can see that you will get
to see some such interface.  And
in identity proof you have to select PAN card.
And here you have to fill the PAN card number.
And after that you have to upload a photo of the PAN card.
And
you have to choose the PAN card photo from the gallery.
So friends, you have to click on the save option.
So friends, your PAN
card photo will be uploaded.  Similarly,
in address proof you have to select
passport, voter ID or driving
license or Aadhar card.  So friends, you have to
select the Aadhar card and here
you have to fill the four digits on the back of the Aadhar card.
Last four digits and here you have to
upload the front photo and back photo of the Aadhar card
and after uploading you have to tick the check
and click on the proceed option.   I have to
wait a little.
So friends, finally you can see that
our KYC has been completed and now
you have to come back and then after a day you have to
open the Gmail ID again and
in it you will get to see an email
KYC information you are a two wheeler, you have to click on this you will
see some such interface,
scroll down and you will
see an option need help log in
your account manage your policy
you have to click on the option so friends
you will get to see some such interface and here
you can also get the option of login so
friends you have to fill the mobile number and
send the OTP.  OTP has to be verified.
So friends, you will see some such interface
that you have insured.
So friends, you have to click on this.
So friends, you can see that two
insurances are coming in this.  One from 15 lakhs Extend
cover and one from your Echo Toko.  So friends,
you have to click on this.  So friends,
you have to allow this.  And in this you
can see that you will get a copy of your policy.  You
can also download it.  And
your mail will also be included in it.  So you can download it through mail also.
In this you will get both the
mails.  You can also download your accident cover of Rs 15 lakh
and Ripokyo insurance policy
and you will also
receive it by mail.  You can also download it through mail.
So friends, in this way
you can very easily complete the bike insurance pending KYC of Policy Bazaar
and download the insurance policy.
So friends, I hope
you liked the video.
Like and share the video.  If you are new to the channel,
please subscribe to the channel.  So
friends, see you again
with the next video.  Till then Jai Hind, Jai
Mahadev.